hamstersoft.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy policy for the www.hamste-rsoft.com

## Privacy policy for the global www.hamstersoft.com site

**Privacy policy**

Privacy Policy of [www.hamstersoft.com](http://www.hamstersoft.com/) web sites - the Site(s) This Privacy Policy applies to these Site(s). When leaving any Site(s), please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are thereafter visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site(s). Entering and using the Site(s) you declare your agreement with this privacy statement. By using these Site(s), you expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that your Personal Information gained with registration on these Site(s), or in connection with your use of the Site(s), with respect to the Site(s), may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site(s) (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration) for operating and developing the Site(s), including transfers to HamsterSoft subcontractors, agents or representatives, who perform tasks related to the Site(s) and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant databases. 

**Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected**

HamsterSoft is committed to the protection of privacy of the Site(s) visitors. Please note that HamsterSoft may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to trusted third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. 

**Personal Information**

HamsterSoft collects Personal Information for the purposes of provision, development and personalization of the Site(s) and any other HamsterSoft sites, services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics and customer care. Specifically, HamsterSoft collects personal information for the purposes of personal communication with you in order to respond to your questions, and fulfill your requests. Such information may include, among other information, your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. These data will be used in the events you have so consented, to contact you for direct marketing purposes via mail, e-mail or phone to conduct market research, and to inform you of and get your feedback on upcoming products, services and/or promotions. If you send us product orders, service requirements or if you send any material to the Site(s), we might have to contact you in order to gain additional information necessary for processing or fulfillment of your orders and/or requirements. Your Personal Information will not be revealed to any third parties without your prior consent, unless required otherwise by legal regulations, or cases, when it is necessary for proceeding of your order, fulfilling of your request, or providing interactive customer service and HamsterSoft's products and services improvement. At the same time you are granting HamsterSoft the right to provide the information you submitted to HamsterSoft for above purposes to the partners cooperating with HamsterSoft. 

**Personal Information Security**

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or any other media or terminal, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker-proof", HamsterSoft has endeavored to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your Personal Information. For example when collecting or transferring sensitive data, e.g. cash card information, we use encrypting technology. 

**Accuracy of Collected Data**

HamsterSoft will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any in-complete, inaccurate or outdated personal information retained by HamsterSoft in connection with the operation of the Site(s). 

**Visitors Identification**

Generally, you may use these Site(s) for information purposes without giving personal information and informing HamsterSoft who you are. But, from time to time, HamsterSoft or its third-party designees may place information on your computer to allow HamsterSoft to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as "cookies". The cookies are commonly used on many websites. Cookies are stored on your hard disc in the computer, not on the Site(s). HamsterSoft or its third-party designees will use only information, they themselves placed in cookies through the Site(s) or other HamsterSoft's web sites. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. By means of cookies HamsterSoft is able to further develop and improve the Site(s). As to the former, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type your log-in name each time and without having to add products to your shopping list each time in between two visits, if the transaction was not finished in previous visit. No personal information about you is gathered through the use of these types of cookies. In other words, cookies are identifying your computer, not you. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or you want to be notified when a cookie is set, you can configure your browser, if the browser allows given settings. If you choose to decline cookies, please, be aware, that you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site(s), nor you will be able to download certain contents and/or to take part in certain transactions on the Site(s). Besides, the Site(s) may use different technology, which enables to HamsterSoft to collect certain technical information, for example: your IP address, type of operational system in your computer, internet browser type and addresses of connected sites, in order to improve provided services. 

**Minors**

No information may be submitted to HamsterSoft via the Site(s) by persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to HamsterSoft via the Site(s), with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country. 

**Modification of the Privacy Policy**

HamsterSoft reserves the right to change or modify at any time this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or deny access to the Site(s), or their content without prior notice. 

**Service Specific Terms**

HamsterSoft may have separate terms for different services (for example the Terms of Usage), in which the service specific terms and conditions might be set forth (including data protection).
